Emotional Melodies for a story 20+ Tracks
This package is trial version.

Check full version of this Package.
https://assetstore.unity.com/packages/slug/153921


Best inspiring and impressive game tracks for a story of your own game.

Romantic and Emotional tracks. 
This perfectly fits for storytelling scenes, boss battles, events, movie trailers.
In this package you'll find 24 instrumental tracks.
All of the wav tracks are available as high quality 16 bit, and high quality re-mastered for using in games.
And, this pack includes ogg seamless loop with all music tracks.


------------------

Content

04. Last Confession
15. Blue Garnet

Produced by ISAo.
http://airyluvs.com
isao@airyluvs.com

*If you want to order new music or arrangement, please contact to me :)

Thanks.
2019/9/11
